(dinging)
(speaking in foreign language)
(suspenseful music)
- Hi everybody, Andy here.
You might remember me from the droppers of line
Club 5 Summer Holiday compilation part one
that we released two weeks ago.
Well, today's the day.
Here's part two.
So just to recap briefly,
this is a summer holiday compilation
of bits of droppers of line that were cut out,
unjustly many of them.
Many of them good bits where I said something,
you know, I was introducing something well
or I had a brilliant fact
or you know, made a really funny joke.
Dan edits these and he cut out a lot of them.
So I've asked him to put them back in,
please all of them.
So here's part two.
Normal service will resume and we've got a proper introduction
from you in a couple of weeks time
for another episode of droppers of line.
Bye for now.
Happy summer.
- Hi.
- Hey Andy.
- Always doubt, always doubt with James.
- I try and say hi with my eyes.
(laughing)
Hello, do you really lost it now?
You've done it.
You've thrown off the first recording of the year.
- It's my job.
- I hope you're happy.
- That's all I try and do on this show.
- What should we start with?
- Anything related to the show that we do.
- Not really, that's not what the listener wants.
The listeners have been very clear in the inbox
about what they want.
And what they want is to send maybe a hundred suggestions
for the name of the book of things related to.
- You say it's not what the listener wants,
but I can't help but notice it's the same five recurring names
each week.
- Where are the emails out from?
- Very determined listeners we've got, I guess.
Should it be called Crypto Eponyms?
- Sure.
- It's not catchy.
- A lot of people have suggested it.
Two people within one minute of each other in the inbox.
- Yeah.
- What are we saying?
- I'm not saying anything.
Your job is to find the coincidence.
- Okay.
- To call them out.
- John G. Erickson and Ryan Boyce
both made the same suggestion within one minute
of each other.
Crypto Eponyms.
- Locations where are we writing from?
- They don't say, they don't say.
- We talked about the podcast that we recorded today
about Twins, how sometimes Twins, they're brought up apart,
but they still have this kind of bond between them.
So these two people that you've mentioned,
perhaps they were twins that were split up at birth,
but they still have that sort of psychic connection.
They have the same idea and email the same podcast
with the same stupid idea.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- You can't call it.
What?
- Spiky.
- What happened?
- You said it was a stupid idea for a book, weird.
- Sorry, because I started talking
and I knew I had to get to the end of it
and then my brain just went on autopilot.
- I do the same the whole time.
I don't know if you've ever noticed.
Phonyms, like FAUX.
- Oh yeah.
- That's from Joseph.
If you're it's a plan on phonyms.
I think phonyms might not be well known
enough as a word to...
- I think it's well known as a word,
but that's not what it means.
- Disgreponyms.
- Thanks to Joe Stevenson for that one.
- What about Trisha Thea from Omaha's suggestion?
Epiphonyms.
It's a combination of epiphony and eponym.
Namefakes, like namesakes.
That's for pooja Venkatraman.
- The problem with these, some of these is like namefakes.
- Yeah.
- On the title of the book,
you have to put in brackets, like namesakes.
- Yeah, I'll just explain this to you.
- It's one leap, exactly.
- Nate Martin, unexpectedly eponymous.
One thousand and one things you would never guess
are named after people.
- Sorry Nate, that's not actually not the point of the book.
It's not that they're unexpectedly named after people.
It's that they're that, but they also sound like
the thing that they do.
Genuinely, there are 30 more people who suggested titles
for the book.
- Really?
- So we'll become completely unmovable
if we do them all, but they're brilliant, thank you.
- Ideally, you want a word that sounds like it's describing
what the book is, but it's actually named after someone,
like a word that is what it does.
- Yeah, the name hunter, but actually it's the name hunter.
- Yeah, but it sounds like you're hunting for names.
- But it is my name, yeah.
- That's very good.
Someone did suggest, call it Andy Murray's book
of interesting names, but it's not that Andy Murray.
- That's completely different from what James was saying.
- Was it it?
- Yeah.
- Completely as a bit of a stretch.
- What are you saying is name hunter?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you're hunter.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- No, I get it.
- That's very far from, what about Andy Murray's book?
- I see that now.
- I do see that now.
- Hey, wonderful section.
- Let's have some bonus brain.
- James, I didn't make the edit.
- Katelyn Martin writes, "I'm thrilled that my time has come
to write in and even more so thrilled to use it
as an opportunity to dunk on Wyoming."
- Oh, that's nice Wyoming.
- Well, in a recent episode,
you were discussing the lack of escalators in the state,
and I lit up with some additional details to share,
growing up in Colorado.
- Okay.
- Okay, not far.
- Yeah, is that close?
- Next door.
- Up north.
- We have a neighborly dislike in general of Wyoming
from one square state to another.
I spent a semester studying at the University
of Wyoming in Laramie, and one day was informed
that my five-story dormitory was the tallest building
in the state.
- Wow.
- This was added to the list of many other details
and circumstances that motivated me to transfer elsewhere.
- There you go.
- Katelyn.
- Okay.
- There was a much there apart from I hate Wyoming.
- Yeah.
- I just think we should spend the New Year starting some fights
between American states.
America seems very harmonious at the moment,
and I don't know if you should stir the pot.
- Jasper Diedlichsen from Northern Germany, right?
Dear Fischteam, just listened to your latest episode
in which you talked about football chance
being composed by famous composers.
- Yeah.
- Which we did as a joke.
- Yeah, although Elgard did write the first one.
- Good point.
I have lived in Hamburg, Germany for quite some time,
but only recently made it to St. Paulie Stadium to watch a game.
And was delighted to hear the fans use the triumph
for March from Giuseppe Verdi's Ida for one of their chance,
which is forza St. Paulie.
Being more of an opera ultra than a football supporter,
I turned to one of the fans and asked,
"Isn't that Verdi?"
Only to see bewildered faces in return.
- Very good.
- It is nice.
Rob Beckett used to do a bit of standup
about how him and his father-in-law
were quite culturally different.
He was into football.
His father-in-law was into opera, right?
He took him into the opera and he was like,
"Oh, this is League of Champions theme tune."
"Oh, this is ski Sunday."
(all laughing)
- Well, actually, is it insurance darts?
Is you'll never walk alone.
- Oh, really?
- Is insurance darts, I think.
Is it?
No, it isn't.
Wait a minute, no, Ness and Dahmer.
Sorry.
- Is that so?
- But Ness and Dahmer, which was like a big football thing,
is insurance darts.
- Right.
- So.
- Yeah.
- I like insurance darts.
- I bet it's good.
- It's very good.
- Well, now, the Royal Opera is, I think so.
- It's the big, it's the big fight scene
in Mission Impossible Fives, near the start.
- Which is in the opera.
- That's the thing.
- When I went to watch Mission Impossible Five
in a cinema, I leaned over to the person next to me
and said, "Is this Puccini?"
(all laughing)
- Raphael writes, "The story James told
about junior senior playing movie feet four times,
instantly reminded me of the time,
Kanye West and Jay Z.
(all laughing)
I know.
- Put out a song called, I actually can't say this.
- Okay.
- It's N words in Paris.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- Big song.
- They did a show in Paris where they performed it 12 times.
- Whoa.
- I think they were trying to set a record
for playing that song.
I think they won the record.
- Is it their song?
- I believe so.
- It's hard to imagine anyone else being in that record.
- Yeah.
(all laughing)
- Coldplay.
- Swooped in.
- But you're not gonna say, no, we're gonna say all the words.
- It won't count unless we do.
(all laughing)
- All right, we'll stay with one slightly blue fact.
- Not blue, but it's slightly rude and crude.
- Yeah.
- It's from Bo Ellsworth, who writes,
in relation to something on the Ben Ells and show,
a few weeks ago now.
- Yes.
- When I was a missionary from my church,
the church of Jesus Christ of the latter day sayings.
- Moments.
- So sometimes now.
- That's true.
- Although they do email in if you'd say that.
- I'm just saying that sometimes now.
- Absolutely.
- I'm not saying I call them that.
- Okay, fair point.
- Podcast at QR.com.
(all laughing)
When I was a missionary for my church in Brazil,
- Wow.
- There were men who rode around collecting urine
from nuns to make soap.
- Ah.
- Oh.
- When the, when none urine was in short supply,
they would approach our sister missionaries,
the girls, and try and convince them to donate their urine.
These collectors did not appear to come
from reputable pharmaceutical companies,
or even an ethically questionable beautician company.
As far as I could tell,
they were just guys making soap out of piss.
- How do you make soap out of?
You would need some, oh.
- I don't know.
- But they're not.
- Say.
- Bowe doesn't relate.
- You know, Google it.
- Bowe's, no, I didn't Google it.
Podcast at QR.com.
(all laughing)
- Yeah, I don't know how that would work.
- Me neither.
- Doesn't really,
wouldn't have any fats in it, you know, would it?
- No, you're right.
- Weirdo's in Brazil.
- That's a great extra fact though, to the nun urine.
- Yeah.
- Well, it's bang on target, isn't it?
It's relevant.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's really good.
- You've just been to Wells?
- I'm sure.
- Wells, been to Tombridge Wells.
- I think you made an Instagram video in Wells.
- Did I?
- The longest street, or the medieval street?
- Oh, is that in Wells?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I have been there.
(all laughing)
- I can't believe it.
- I always forget these different diets.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I have only been to Wells, that's why.
But yeah, they have a street that goes towards the cathedral.
But it's got an illusion in it.
So it makes it look shorter when you're on one end
and longer when you're on the other,
because the house is moving.
- Yeah, right.
- Was that on the floor?
- No, I was on holiday,
and they just dragged my long-suffering life and daughter there.
- Oh, it's beautiful.
- It's really nice.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- A lot of hot fuzz, of course, with film drama.
- How is it?
- Yeah.
- They've got in the pub.
They've got the flat jackets
that they wore in that pub shootout scene.
- You're right.
- They've got a few other things.
- Oh, that's really cool.
- Ben Hopkinson.
Salman Rushdie has not published music with Kylie Minogue,
but he did collaborate with you too
on the ground beneath her feet.
Oh, yeah, that was one of his novels.
- Is that true?
- Not sure, but that's one of his novels.
- That's why I'm asking you.
That's how I'm fair, you haven't had time to prep.
- Yeah.
Perhaps this can be filed under a new subcategory.
Salman Facts.
Salman.
- Salman.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Really good.
- Yes.
- Sheamus from Monahan in Ireland writes,
I've just listened to the latest little fish.
You've hit the nail on the head.
And I can't believe you missed an open goal.
In the conversation about golfers only wearing one glove,
I waited and waited for the obvious joke,
but I was left disappointed.
- Did you guys actually get a hole in one?
- Oh, that's good.
- Like, that's the old joke.
Why did golfer wear two pairs of trousers
in case he got a hole in one?
- But it would be more like, why would the golfer
wear three gloves?
Not one glove.
- Oh yeah.
- Because you couldn't wear one glove in case
you got a hole in one.
And also they've got six holes in anyway, haven't they?
- Yeah, no.
- Give us, give us the,
let's just rewind that a second.
- Fingalous gloves?
- I assume golfers gloves are fingalous.
- I think not.
- Not to begin with by the end.
- I hope you won them for a while, they do get it.
- I assume there were for some reason.
I've got, because I have cyclist gloves at home
which are all fingalous.
- Oh yeah.
- So they've got six holes in.
But your golfers gloves you're saying
have only got one hole.
- Just to put the hand in here.
- Like a shipworm.
Yeah.
- Anyway, what's the,
what's the setup that we can get the answer?
- Okay, golfers only wear one glove because,
because, I don't know.
- I think this is getable for too many minds like yours.
This should be child's play.
Only wear one glove.
- Acaster and gamble.
- They would already be on the next course,
but on the next episode, yeah.
- I just feel like I've heard every golf joke there is.
- I bet you've heard this one.
- Yeah.
- Golfers only wear one glove because, do you give up?
- No.
- Can we cut all this dead air out?
Yeah, good.
- But I will cut the answer to it.
- I'm telling you, golfers wear only one glove
because on the one hand, it might be cold,
but on the other hand, it may be warm.
- Yeah, okay.
- Shema said, as a recently retired headmaster,
I'd like to say, I'm not annoyed.
I'm just disappointed you've let yourself down.
Shema, so you haven't seen because we've,
we've edited the show down,
but these guys sat in silence for I'd say 20 minutes.
- I thought it was gonna be golf related.
- But you said it hasn't got a hand in it.
So I thought--
- Yeah, but also in no situation on the golf course,
you're either really cold or you're too hot.
Like, I've never been in a situation
where one of my hands is too hot
and the other one's too cold.
It's just not realistic at all.
- Well, we've criticised Shema's joke there
and I think he'll think twice before saying that again.
- What situation have you ever been in
where one of your hands has you just put it in hot oil?
- It's ridiculous.
- Well, okay, yeah, nonsense.
I'm feeling sour grapes being served up here.
A couple of silly ones now.
- Okay, great.
- Here's one for the theory realm.
- Love.
- That's a new realm.
- Who's asking rights?
- How they sign off there even?
- Yeah, okay.
- Who's asking?
- Bit aggressive.
Here's a fact for you.
- The big--
- What?
- Nothing, nothing.
- You look at me with this grin like,
oh, let's just see Andy Coat with, you know.
- That's a smile of admiration.
- It's not, I've never seen you do.
I would recognize him as a sneaker of admiration.
- It's weird 'cause I've got a lot of material.
I should be able to fall back on the reams of paper
I bring along every time.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You've got nothing.
You guys are going in nude every time.
- Well, just that lemon.
- It's crazy how good you guys are on this show
and how bad I am.
- You're giving them that I hold all the cards.
(laughing)
- It's nuts.
Who's asking rights?
Here is a fact for you.
The big crunch, the end of the universe
if some theories are correct,
is much closer than most people realize.
- Oh, within most of our lifetimes, in fact.
(laughing)
- The evidence.
After the big fishbang in March 2014,
four facts have been created per week.
- Oh, I see.
- But since November 2025,
facts have been doled out to subscribers
at a rate of eight per week.
- I see.
- At this rate, we'd run out of facts by early 2037.
- Yeah.
- But how many subscribers to a friend of the podcast
where we need at that stage?
- Well, we'll have needed, oh goodness.
- It'll be in the thousands, right?
- It'll be in the thousands of thousands, yeah, yeah.
- Well, I also, your spreadsheet has
tens of thousands of facts on it.
- That's true.
- Not all of them are headlines.
- Most of them up.
- Yeah, so if we ever did get to the end of the headlines,
then we can start doling out some of our better
non-head headlines.
- Yeah, that's a really good point.
So maybe we'll be all right.
- Yeah, I think so.
- It's a long way away.
I'm not worried.
- I have a spare 10,000 facts from our books.
- Oh, yeah.
- The QI fact books that we did.
- That's a good.
- That's a spare, just sitting there.
- Well, there's 10,000 in there.
- Yeah.
- Those books.
- Oh, in the books, right?
I thought you meant that you didn't use
for those books.
- Oh.
- It's top of it.
- 'Cause I know you have a secret fact doc that
- I do, and that is pretty healthy as well.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Many thousands in there.
- Wow.
- For any of you who wants to just see me in the street
and give me some cash, I'll let you have one of those facts.
- That's nice.
- Free-lancing.
- How much are you charging?
- Yeah, yeah.
- 'Cause I'm actually interested in getting a few myself.
- Well, you need them for next week's show, didn't you?
- Exactly.
- What time you live in the building?
(laughing)
- I had it at the door the other day.
- I'd heard about this on the book,
our three being celebrated,
but I didn't believe it was real.
A Jordy Fishman coming to the door.
I was saying, "Would you like to buy some fish?"
And I'd never had that before in my whole life.
Have you heard that?
- And they always joddies?
- They're always two days.
- Really?
- This was a long-running joke on three being salad,
which I thought, "Oh, these guys are just having a laugh."
And genuinely, a Jordy Fishman came to my door the other day.
And I said, "No, I don't want any fish."
But I'd, interestingly, make a podcast,
which is called, no such thing as a fish,
so maybe you can come up with some section names for me.
(laughing)
Big old bag of fish was actually his idea.
- That's interesting.
- Yeah.
- Anyway.
- That's so weird.
- I didn't know.
It was the thing, Jordy Fishman.
- I know.
- Well, I would have thought that you, from further north,
I know you're not from Newcastle.
- Yeah.
To be honest, the transport links from Newcastle to London,
are probably better than the transport links
from Newcastle to Bolton.
- Oh, interesting.
So I'm likely to have seen the Jordy Fishman
that maybe you would have thought back then.
- Yeah, we have a Fishman who comes round
in Montenegrau.
Just goes, "Reba, reba."
- Jordy.
- It sounds like it doesn't it,
when I say it like that, but no.
"Vindankation from Molly McInerney."
- Oh, okay.
- Is she suggesting this episode,
this section, section title?
- So, "Vindicating Dan."
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- In one episode, Dan is mocked for suggesting
that it is possible to grow a new pineapple
from the top of a pineapple which has been eaten.
- Yeah, did we?
- I'm sure we did.
- Yeah, that sounds like us.
- #Vindankation.
There are plenty of articles and videos online
about how to grow a new pineapple
by planting a leftover pineapple top.
- Yeah, I think where I probably got it wrong,
I didn't know this was coming,
so I haven't looked into this again,
but I thought about it on the way home.
I think you've got to put it into the physical ground,
where as I said, I think you can put it like
in between the branches of a tree
and it will just grow back out.
- Okay.
- But, okay, yeah.
- Have you ever seen a pineapple growing in real life?
- No.
- Very slow.
- Well, they're really interesting
'cause they grow on the ground.
And there's just like a pineapple
and then a load of leaves sort of coming out for them.
- Right.
- They don't grow on a bush, they don't grow on a tree,
they just weirdly have their own little--
- That is right.
- Yes.
- When you first see them,
it's quite something to notice.
- Yeah, but.
- Tom O'Neill has a question.
Who out of the fish team would win Taskmaster
if you were all in the series together?
- I think you, James.
- Depends what the challenge is that.
I would be the one taking it most seriously.
But I think the thing with Taskmaster
is the people who take it really seriously
are usually not the people's favorites.
- Interesting.
- I would just want to do really, really well
because I'm extremely competitive.
But I think really, Taskmaster,
you're not supposed to be like that.
You're supposed to be wacky and funky.
- Ah, in that you see,
I have had a lifetime of losing at games,
which has beaten a lot of the competitors out of me,
but I'm also not wacky or fun.
So I think I would probably,
- You just cut out the series.
(laughing)
- Occasionally you'd see.
- It was an extra chair.
- It was a wide shot of your city.
- Someone was in that chair, but it's too hot to.
- That must be a task.
It must be one of Alex's tricks,
where in the last episode they were revealed
that he was here all along.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- So probably Dana Rennor.
He Ben writes,
"After listening to the London Podcast Festival episode
with Jamie and the segment about spars,
I wanted to offer something for your consideration,
and I thought I would attempt to do so
in true Harkinian style.
Which do you think there are more of in the UK?
Spars?
- Records.
- Relaxation.
- Oh, I see.
- Well, spars.
- Records.
- Convenient grocery stores.
- I feel like I haven't seen a spar for quite a few years.
Do they, are they still extant?
- Well, you're now leading a metropolitan London elite lifestyle.
- I thought they turned into summer fields or something,
but I must be wrong.
- I think they do exist.
- I lived near one in Hometon.
That's roughly one of the only ones I even saw
while I was living here.
So for me, it's obviously the other one, spars.
- Obviously.
- I mean, what, you've literally seen a spar?
(laughing)
I mean, how many local spars could you name?
- Tons.
- Okay.
- Yeah, this is the Margate Metropolitan elite lifestyle.
- Yeah, I'm going, I'm going actual spars.
- Okay, James.
- If I go back to Bolton.
- Yeah.
- I know we have a couple of spars.
Spars.
- If we can't, we have to bring it up.
- But I don't, I can't think of any spars.
- Thank you, okay.
- In Bolton, there might be one, but I just don't,
if there is, I don't recall where it is.
And then if I extrapolate throughout the rest of the country,
(laughing)
it has to be the wellness retreat that there's most of.
- So you're both saying the wellness retreat?
- Yeah.
- What a, what a low jeopardy.
(laughing)
Well, it might not be, it might be very high jeopardy.
You might have both absolutely stuffed it.
- Yeah.
- Have we?
- No.
(laughing)
- Of course we haven't.
- Have we both answered the extremely easy question correctly?
- It's not as, it's closer than you'd think.
- All right.
- I think it's like relatively close.
- Yes, that's, I think that's what I just,
I think that's what I just said.
(laughing)
- I think you said it's closer than that.
- Oh, okay.
- Well, it's as close as you think,
which is relatively close.
- It's, you're both correct that it's spars,
that there are more of, as of 2020.
- So that's, that's spars, not spars.
- I'll say spars if it's spars.
His figures are from 2020,
which I think is dangerous the out of date.
'Cause a lot of those spars would have closed down
during COVID, as would, as would spars.
Sparras are an essential way of providing groceries
to people.
- Yeah, but the growth of a cardo
over there since the pandemic could have put pay
to a lot of sparras.
- I do, yeah, no.
Well, as of 2020,
there were 3,671 spars, brackets relaxation,
and there were a mere 2,190 sparras.
- That's way more than I thought it would be.
- It's way more, and that's why I said it was relatively close.
Yeah.
Ben rounds off, no information as yet on how many sparrs,
brackets, practice boxing fights,
all sparras, large pieces of wood for bracing things.
- There are.
- But the Belgium town of sparr,
there's definitely only one of those.
- Yes, but does it contain a sparrer?
- Probably not.
Anyway, brilliant quiz.
Thank you, Ben.
I think one question quiz.
- Yeah, thanks, Ben.
- What's your final score?
- It's one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
- Is there a tie breaker question?
- No.
- Okay, this is a bit flawed.
- Well done.
- Oh, yeah.
Excellent work.
- Good game.
- You guys did pretty well
and that you both got the one correct question.
- That was correct.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, rodeo clap number one.
- Oh, okay.
- And we've had 15 emails about this.
I'm only gonna read one.
Richard Hannie says, with reference to,
you remember that dog tumour that is 11,000 years old?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- And Dan had the moment of his career.
You came up with the best joke you ever have
or ever welcome on.
- Too messy bark.
- Okay.
Richard Hannie says,
I'm sure you've had this email 1,000 times by now, 15.
But Jurassic Park is an extremely well known
and brilliant episode of Futurama,
where Fry discovers the fossilized remains of his beloved dog
and sees if he can bring him back to life.
- Okay.
- Well, I don't think you knew that already.
- No, what's the point being made?
- As long as you stole their joke.
- Oh, wow.
But what I think that says to me is,
what brilliant joke writers
the people who make Futurama are.
- Absolutely, yeah.
- Absolutely.
- Great minds.
- Great hints for another rider.
- I agree.
- Hit me up.
- Yes.
Tim says, I did not laugh at your joke.
Not because it wasn't exactly as brilliant
as you represented on the show,
but because I have seen the Futurama episode
and was therefore weeping at the thought,
apparently it's an unbelievably sad episode of Futurama.
Despite my nearly ruined walk to work,
I will still listen and recommend you to everyone I know,
even as that pool becomes ever smaller once they listen.
- Yeah.
Because they will already know about the show.
- Oh, I see.
I thought it was like, I know fewer people
because I recommend it and then I don't know them anymore.
Yours makes a lot more sense.
- I still think it was a great joke.
- Okay.
- And you had another one later on in that show
and that was also brilliant.
- Did I?
- Can't remember it.
Yeah, you did.
- Okay.
- But it wasn't quite as good.
- Okay, well thanks.
- Mona Wu or writes in with you said it wrong.
- Oh.
- That's a pronunciation thing.
- It is.
Correct.
It is.
Mona listened to the assistant honcho episode,
which was where we talked about Emily Dickinson.
- Okay.
That was a long time ago.
- Some years ago.
- Yeah.
- Emily Dickinson was alive and well.
(laughing)
- Oh, this episode.
- American poet.
- Yeah.
- Like to hyphen.
- Did she?
- Well, she didn't like something we did during this episode
or she wouldn't have liked it.
I'm a professor at Amherst College
and wanted to share a small correction.
Here, Amherst is pronounced Amherst without the H.
- Amherst.
- There's even a local saying.
- Amherst, where only the H is silent.
And that's because apparently the town's population
are very outspoken.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- That's nice.
I've only ever seen that written down.
Amherst, or Amherst.
- Amherst.
- Yeah.
- And Mona points out this is a very minor addition
to the story list of famous fish mispronunciations.
Who could have forgotten a lable plane?
Or who?
Who?
I'd tell you when I had to say it now.
Houston?
- Houston.
- Yeah.
- No, no, Houston.
- Not Houston.
- Okay.
- There you go.
She finishes with an extra little kick.
I'd also been maintaining a list
of mispronounced bacterial species.
But since I still sometimes struggle to say the escheric here
in E. coli.
- E. coli.
Despite studying it, I don't have a leg to stand on.
Thank you, Mona.
- Very nice.
- It's a fair point.
It's Mona.
- Mona.
- The Mona Lisa.
- Yeah.
- Carol.
- Is it really?
- No.
- Okay.
Radio clan number two.
- Yeah.
- Kevin Smith.
- Cattle can indeed swim.
- Yeah, great.
- I think we did a call out saying
if you can't swim in Cal photo and we had a lot.
- I knew this would happen.
- We have to stop saying it.
I'm sure it was me who said it.
We have to stop saying if you've got a photo of something.
- It was me who said it because I was like,
"Oh, a few weeks ago, we asked if people had a picture
of a flying chicken and we got loads of messages in.
Let's get the farmyard crew back."
- Oh, this was when I was saying a cow swim
under the tunnel that was either a mile
or just a rameyla, just a rameyla?
- Oh, my God.
- Made it to the show, did it?
- Yeah, I guess.
- Have you got the photo?
- No, I haven't, but they were just going
to the inbox yourself, mate.
- It's just going to be a cow in a river.
There's nothing going to be any surprise in there.
- No, I just don't like cows so much, that is.
- Well, you've got a treat waiting for you in the inbox.
A lot of cow photos.
- Daniel Levitt writes that a new form of propeller
was designed to protect marine life by Dr. Fish.
However, it gets better because there are two other
common vendors who I looked up and it's a triple nom to term.
So, it's a new propeller to protect marine life, right?
Dr. Fish is one of the three of us months before it.
Also, it was designed by Philip Watts.
- Okay.
- What propellers use electricity?
What's electricity measured in?
- Watts.
- Does this one use electricity?
Is not powered by the water or?
- Didn't check.
- Okay.
(laughing)
In fairness, you still have a wattage of anything, really?
- Right.
That's my reasoning.
And Stephen Dua and the D-E-W-A-R,
and that it turns out is a fishing cast from India.
- As in a cast, a group of people who fish.
- Like the cast, the cast system, if you like.
- Like the cast of EastEnders.
(laughing)
- Cast of EastEnders.
- Wow.
- Okay, well, I would say fish was the strondler of the three.
- I can see why Daniel Levitt led with Dr. Fish
rather than Philip Watts or Stephen Dua.
That's all me, by the way.
What the other two names were all me.
Daniel's an innocent contributor to this.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, thank you.
- But the thing is, Daniel, Andy would not have read that out
if he hadn't done his own work
and thought I've got a triple threat here.
- Yeah, that's true.
That's very true.
Well, the same goes to Emma who writes in
about the woman sanctioned by police
for being out foraging mushrooms.
Her name was Louise Gather.
- Oh, that's good.
But where are you not allowed to get mushrooms?
- She had been searching for a particular kind of mushrooms.
- Oh, those kinds, okay.
- No, no, no.
I think it's very unclear why she was,
I mean, she shouldn't have been told up by the police.
Is the natural threat.
Anyway, the woman who wrote in with this email
is called Emma Leak.
Like the vegetable?
- Well, absolutely not related to mushrooms.
Not shrimps are more closely related to animals
than they are to plants.
- That's plow on.
At two in the amount.
But they're both growing the...
They're both growing the ground.
- Well, one grows in the ground, yeah.
- Oh my god.
- Which one grows it?
Leaks.
- Well, in their parts of the onion family,
so I assume they grow in the ground.
- I've not seen a leak growing.
- Now, because they're on the ground.
Have you ever seen a leak?
- PocasticQI.com.
But they're so clean.
It doesn't make any sense.
- Wonderful to watch.
- I feel like I was in that two-way mirror at Bakery
watching James interrogate you.
I normally have my breakdown a bit later,
so it's weird that it's happening now.
Laura writes that her maiden name is Warwick,
and her middle and first name is Laura and Anne.
Her initials, therefore...
- Laura...
- Laura and Warwick.
- Laura.
- She's a police officer of 20 years service.
Unfortunately, I got married four years ago,
brackets in terms of nominative determinism, not my life.
(laughing)
- To someone with the name and the beginning with G,
so she's, no, she's a lag.
- No, she's now a lad instead.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah, but anyway, thank you, Laura.
Really good.
Laura, if she was called Laura Norder,
if Norder was her surname.
- Yeah.
- Jeff Prairie writes, in 1962,
long before many U.S. states started to decriminalize
marijuana use, the state of Wisconsin established
the BONG recreation area outside the town of Brighton.
Okay, it's actually the Richard BONG state recreation area,
but the sign set is BONG recreation area.
- And was it a place where people partocked?
- No, I don't think so.
I mean, I'm not saying no, whenever it has,
but it is good.
Jeff done a lot of work to make that work,
and it's a funnily named place,
so I think it deserves a credit.
He was called Major Richard Dick BONG,
one of the most highly decorated American fighter pilots
of the Second World War, a serious person.
- The Chimes of Big Ben are named after him as well, aren't they?
- That's right, that's right.
- Yep.
- Well, he downed 40 Japanese aircraft.
- Did he?
- Wow, that's quite a lot.
- Yeah.
- It's 40 more than I...
(laughing)
- It wouldn't be appropriate for me to down-travel,
it would have been way more inappropriate if you said,
"That's 37 more than I have."
(laughing)
- I've gone, okay.
- Yeah.
- James and Chaffield proposes the name just a minnow
for the "I'm Actually" section,
or maybe renamed the whole show.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- James, at this stage, I think it's a bit late.
- Yeah.
- I'm clear where the dropper, he means droppers align,
or nice such thing as a fish,
maybe renamed just a minnow.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
But it's good to have another name in the locker.
So thank you, James.
- David Jones is a locker.
- Brilliant.
Donna Simon just adds a little extra note,
'cause we've talked about, you know,
this is one of those names,
this is a Tacco bell that we've mentioned this,
named after a man named Glen Bell.
- Ah, okay.
- But the logo does have a bell on it.
And she adds, and since you asked,
I could do without more section naming.
- Oh, now.
- Wow, seriously. - Finally.
Someone on my wavelength.
- That's, wow.
- Balance.
This is editorial balance.
- That's good.
- One tiny thing right at the end,
to say not everyone loves this, actually.
But she says, "Love the show."
- It looks to me like you're on your last page.
- Well, I missed a few here, I missed a few here, so.
It all depends on whether people are nice to me or not,
I'd say in these critical final minutes.
- Thank you.
- For everything you do.
- You're welcome, James.
- Love heart.
- You can go.
(laughing)
- Dan, we're gonna do another 20 minutes of a phrase.
- Oh no.
- Do you remember I saw a lady reading your book once,
and I ran back after her and made her take a photo
so that I could send it to you.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- She was fine about it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- You've got to say anything.
Did you get yourself out of that situation?
- Yeah, I'm fine about it.
- Great.
(laughing)
- This is so funny.
Most celebrities, if you chat to them,
they're all about times that they've interacted
with members of the public who wanted to come
and take photos of stuff.
But with us, it's always like,
"Yeah, I met this person and they'd left as quickly
as they possibly could."
(laughing)
- I, at Waterstones, a few weeks ago,
I bumped into someone who was buying a coffee
of one of my books and I asked to have my picture taken with him.
And the guy said, "Normally,"
the guy behind the television picture said,
"Normally, it's the other way around."
- I did that actually and someone recognized me
on the Moscow Tube and asked for a photo.
And I said, "Well, can I also have a photo with you
because this is so unusual that someone would recognize
me on the Moscow Tube."
- Right.
- I think what we're trying to say is we're humble.
(laughing)
We are.
I had one in London a while ago where this guy came up,
took a photo and was going on about what a big fan he was.
Very, very cool.
Walked off final sentence was,
"Hope you in between, just get back together sometimes soon."
(laughing)
- Yep.
Okay.
We'll try.
- Yeah.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- You've done this before.
- I've done it before.
I've actually, I'm actually hot on the heels of quite an embarrassing
moment I had on the train on the way into this recording.
- Please, please tell us.
Where I was on a round train 'cause I've been a train screw up
and there was a woman up against me and she was just looking
at me and she kept on saying, "I really recognize you.
"Why do I recognize you?"
She hammered on, okay.
'Cause that was a huge hour when I was saying.
- Yeah, yeah.
- She was like, "Where do I know you from?"
A few and eventually I said, "As quietly as I possibly could,
I whispered it like I was doing a drug deal."
In fact, I was like, "Do you listen to podcasts?"
And she went, "No, just your daughter,
"swim in a Stevenage swimming pool by any chance."
(laughing)
- And she?
- And she does not.
And that was the end of that conversation.
- So we don't know where she knew you from?
- No, no.
She's seen someone who looked like me at the Stevenage swimming pool.
- Well, that's a cracking anecdote.
And I'll be honest, Anna, it's exactly the kind of thing
we're looking for on Drummer's Align.
(upbeat music)
- That's it for this week's Drummer's Align.
Thank you so much for listening or watching.
If you've enjoyed it, why not contribute?
You lazy so-and-so's?
No, not.
(laughing)
That's it for this week's Drummer's Align.
Thank you so much for listening.
We've really enjoyed it.
And if you'd like to send us an email,
the address is podcast@goi.com,
which I've mentioned several thousand times now
and which really, you should know it off my head by now.
But that's it.
Thank you so much again.
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
- I did the first one.
- The first one.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)